<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>I can&apos;t stop talking!</title>
    
    
    <description>I really can&apos;t stop talking.</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>I won&apos;t July to you...</title>
        <description>
          
          Life Always Happens I don’t mean to sound like Ian Malcolm, but life always finds a way… to interrupt. The truth is, there have been a good bit of serious real world issues since I tried to start this blog at the end of last year. Some of them were...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:10:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-07-20-i-won-t-july-to-you/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-07-20-i-won-t-july-to-you/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>March On By</title>
        <description>
          
          Boy, March really is over huh? Well, I planned to blog weekly, but as with most habits, it’s been a struggle. Nothing personal Life as usual is chaotic, work, family, home-life, etc etc. I did work on quite a bit, I just didn’t record my thoughts on what I worked...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:07:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-04-04-march-by/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-04-04-march-by/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the thick of it</title>
        <description>
          
          Boy Howdy Still trying to get into the habit of blogging, of sharing really. I’m in the middle of one project and starting another, I’m taking some photos, but I’m also still trying to get in a better habit of taking pictures and writing down my thoughts. One day at...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-03-16-stuck-in-the-middle/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-03-16-stuck-in-the-middle/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ice-Worm</title>
        <description>
          
          Wonderful worm I tried to start something and got distracted. That’s sort of my thing, way more often than I’d like. Despite good intentions of starting a game of Frostgrave with my wife a year ago, I got sidetracked many, many times. After painting dozens of models to try and...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:06:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-03-07-ice-worm/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-03-07-ice-worm/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Entry</title>
        <description>
          
          Intro I pushed my self to be a bit more brave and interactive than I usually am, and decided to enter a painting contest. Full disclosure: this was not a high stakes project. One Page Rules hosts a monthly painting contest for that months releases. The pictures are due shortly...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-02-11-miner/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-02-11-miner/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dwogan</title>
        <description>
          
          A very mini Christmas I put together a fun little mini diorama as a Christmas gift for my wife. She’s a fan of Wolverine so off and on throughout our relationship I like to occasionally drop a unique or unusual bit of Wolverine kitsch as a present. I wanted to...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-12-28-dwogan/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-12-28-dwogan/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
